Visit turkision.com for more!
So you say you'll
hit us from behind..
...if we break the heathens behind you...
...and attack Mekece, huh?
You're marching to the castle
which is under my protection.
Not to let you tell others
that we hit you from behind
...we are speaking face to face.
If you just go away
...no blood will be shed in vain.
Don't make us to create battlefield here!
The vilest battlefield ever seen, Yakup Bey!
You put the heathens forward
and come behind us like snakes!
Alright then! Let's start the battle then!
Let's see who is the snake and who is the wolf!
Only Allah knows who's going to die...
...if there is to be a battle here!
Kayi may lose the battle. But both Candar...
...and Germiyan will lose too many here!
Those afraid of losing...
...can never reach the victory!
This is not the matter..
...today here.
If we fight each other,
..if we shed blood
...then...
...this hostility will never end.
Next generations will keep killing each other.
No.
And then...
...no Turkish beylics...
...will manage to become a state under one flag.
So, Osman Bey...
Will you stop?
Not for you.
I'll stop for my dreams.
For my dreams.
Good!
Draw your alps back then!
Alps!
Osman Bey, they're playing a game. Don't you see?
Gunduz Bey.
Okay. Whatever you say, Osman Bey.
If I sense any hostility in Mekece
..then...
...all of you will be my enemies!
Whatever army confronts me
...I will never stop!
Mekece Castle..
...isn't the land of heathens!
It won't be hostile to you!
Osman Bey.
Let me host you in my new land.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
Alaaddin! Gunduz Bey! You
go to the tribe with the alps.
I am...
...going to Mekece with Beys.
I'm going to Mekece...
...so I can see what they gave for it.
Come on.
-As you order, my Bey.
Okay, Osman Bey.
Come on, Beys!
What's going on?
Why are they still not attacking?
UIcay, there is no fighting.
Osman is coming to the castle.
Cowards!
If you show your teeth, you have to bite!
They'll make a deal. There will be peace.
What now?
Their deal will be ruined with blood.
Peace is only for losers.
Only the brave can fight.
Osman won't be able to
get out of this castle alive.
The castle is still under Ibrahim Bey's protection.
When Osman loses his head...
...his sons will come for vengeance.
And then the beylics will fight each other.
What are we going to do here, my Bey?
We should see Mekece which
is going to be our property, right?
We won't stop, huh, my Bey?
Even the heathens couldn't stop us.
So I won't be stopped by
a few words of them. Well...
I set Mekece as my prey.
So nobody can stop me.
You'll see Cerkutay.
They won't keep their promise.
They don't intend to stop us only.
The ones working with the heathens against us...
...can do anything to wipe us out of these lands.
With their first mistake, we'll
take the castle from them.
We'll take even their heads.
So...
You should keep your eyes wide open now.
For the conquest of this castle
...you should gather all the information, Cerkutay.
That's the reason why we've come here.
As you order, my Bey.
-As you order, my Bey.
Alps and I will get to know
every corner of our new land-to-be.
Absolutely. Come on.
Mekece...
My sons, are you alright?
-We're fine, mother.
-Thanks to Allah, we're fine.
Where is Osman Bey?
Ibrahim Bey and Yakup Bey
took Mekece under their protection.
My father will be their guest.
We fell into the nest of the evil.
Yet we looked behind and
climbed out of it, Bala Hatun.
My father must have a plan, Gunduz Bey.
Yes. Osman Bey must have a good plan.
Of course, your father has a plan.
But I know the hearts of those people!
You don't take my words seriously, though.
-Gunduz Bey.
-Alaeddin.
Gunduz Bey.
Let us talk the rest at somewhere else.
Come on.
What happened happened.
There is not much else to talk!
Allah, grant me patience.
What happened to you? Are you alright?
I am alright, my rose.
My Shahzade, come on.
Ghazi.
I am heading out to duty.
Look after my Hatun well.
Alright?
Do not worry, my Shahzade.
I can even guard her tent, for sure.
Praise be to my valiant.
Come on then.
Come on.
This Gunduz Bey got grumpy like my mother.
You can not say that!
Did you call your mother grumpy?
I only say the truth!
I saw it! I saw him blowing off his steam!
What will I do with this one, Gonca?
I don't know, Ulgen.
You heard the Shahzade.
Gonca Hatun is entrusted to me.
Do not come close, Ulgen Hatun!
Look at this one.
Don't act mad! Or you will get the slap.
Here.
You are grumpy!
Grumpy!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
So, Osman Bey.
For whom it is intended
and for whom it is destined.
Conquering Mekece Castle
was written in our destiny.
May Allah..
..allow you to rule it..
..with righteously, Ibrahim Bey.
If you make a mistake..
..you will not hold this place for long, alright?
Do not worry about those issues, Osman Bey.
Because of the peace that was granted..
..Mekece will be one of our most wealthy cities.
The trade that goes from west to east..
..will start from this castle.
Lord?
If Osman Bey wants to benefit from this trade..
..he will need your approval.
There is always a stubborn stone..
..that stops a flowing river.
At worst..
..it makes it change the route.
Is your intention to be a
stone on our road, Osman Bey?
Let us know.
Only time and your acts will determine that.
Ibrahim Bey.
Let us wander around..
..Mekece now.
Soon..
..Lords of Iznik and Bursa..
..will join our trade.
Then, the Frontier Marketplace...
...will leave its name for
"Grand Marketplace" if Allah permits.
We will handle the trade..
..in both west and east.
We rather be small..
..than to trade with infidels..
..and grow in these lands.
However..
..I do not want to intervene in your business.
-..if something happens to the
people- -You can not intervene anyways.
Because, we've calculated everything..
..and did what is needed.
You will either stay with us..
..or against us.
As you big brothers..
..we want to give you a piece of our powers.
You are trying to work with infidels.
And you are trying to
make us fall for that as well.
I will never fall for that.
You got us wrong, Osman Bey.
The days when we wanted to
see you with us, were left behind.
From now on..
..you can only be behind us.
And that can only happen with full loyalty.
Loyalty you say.
Loyalty is only provided to a ruler.
You have no rule over us.
Our loyalty is only for our cause.
Catch that dog.
Osman Bey.
You should've let us fight
until the last drop of our blood.
The tricks are big, Gunduz
Bey. They've united with infidels.
Yes.
Now, we need to spill their bloods as well.
We should've defeated that
Germiyanid and that Candar.
Gunduz Bey. Of course, we
will not fall back from fighting.
We will repay them a thousand more.
If I know my father, he thinks like this as well.
You father let this team of dastards walk.
Look at our situation here.
Kayis do not fall from the field of battle!
They do not, Gunduz Bey.
We never ran away from any fight.
However, we always avoided
spilling the blood of our brothers.
-My father- -Alaeddin!
One you avoided spilling
blood of is working with infidels.
Are you refraining because
Germiyan is your father-in-law?
Gunduz Bey.
I do not discriminate.
I never discriminate just
because of father-in-law, know that.
Bala Hatun.
I am going to my tribe. Let Osman Bey know.
Come on. Stay well.
You are still answering to Gunduz Bey..
..instead of keeping it calm, Alaeddin.
Don't you hear what he is saying, brother?
I had to answer. He blamed
me for protecting Yakup Bey.
I've heard what Gunduz Bey said, Alaeddin.
However, I've heard what you
said to Gunduz Bey before as well.
You know the reason why
Gunduz Bey is so angry, right?
You scolded a Bey of tribe in front of alps.
Sons.
Stay calm.
Alaeddin.
You brother is right.
Gunduz Bey is very angry
about what happened lately.
Staying against him in a
time like this will not do.
You need to make peace with him at once.
Alright.
We will send the goods to Bursa tomorrow.
-At a time like this?
-This is my father's command.
We will go to Ulcay's den with Alaeddin.
It is time to make that dog talk.
My father, is making plans to take that castle.
-However, Gunduz Bey is not aware of this.
-Yes.
My Bey was not pleased about
Gunduz Bey's impulsive outburst.
So that's why he was angry.
Alright.
It seems we will have a new castle tomorrow, right?
We will, if Allah permits, mother.
If Allah permits.
You're doing something wrong in the wrong castle.
We know what the Alps who
brought Ahmet Bey's body said.
The killer used the dagger with his right hand.
If he hadn't been angry, using the
dagger would have been enough...
...but it wasn't.
He grabbed his throat with his left hand
and used the dagger with his right hand.
The killer will show his anger again, Osman Bey.
What is this situation?
Osman Bey is our guest in this castle!
Tugay! How did you let this happen?
That was the ruling I was
talking about, Ibrahim Bey.
You talk about ruling...
...but they are challenging you here.
Mehmet.
Do not kill this dog.
What was his purpose by attempting
to kill Osman Bey in our property?
I will learn all this by pulling
those words out of his mouth!
Alps!
Your eyes will be on all
the soldiers in the castle!
If there is such an attack again...
...you will pay for it, Tugay!
Osman Bey!
All my soldiers are under
the command of our laws...
...know that.
Don't try using this attack.
After what I did today, I
hope Osman Bey forgives me.
Your soldiers are loyal to the laws.
But we'll see...
..if you are...
...loyal to the laws...
...or not.
We'll see.
The words we say..
...are now the laws, Osman Bey.
Come on.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
Yakup Bey.
I will go and make that dog speak.
Continue?
Continue what, Cerkutay?
Will you continue walking on the wrong path?
Your way is the only right way, right?
No.
The way is the way of truth, it is not our way.
But... at least we are not
protecting the castle of infidels.
We are conquering castles
without shedding blood, Cerkutay.
Cerkutay... Good.
We conquered many lands, brother.
This conquest...
...this..
...this is preventing the fire of gaza.
If Crusaders are wandering around the yard...
...I cannot call that place our homeland.
Now..
...listen to your conscience...
...and see the truth.
Or else...
...this move will hurt you the most.
Look at my Bala..
She already prepared the dowery, huh?
My mother started preparing the dowry before
my brother was able to confess his love.
Right!
But he used to say he was not in love then...
But now we are preparing their dowry, huh?
This was not necessary, Bala Hatun.
Why, my daughter?
It is not even enough for my children.
Gonca...
Come... Come.
My daughter...
You sacrificed great things for this love.
There is a fire in your heart that
gets stronger every time a wind blows.
I can see it.
Can't I put this fire out?
I... was used to my mother and brother.
But my father..
I... used to...
...run away from everything and
everyone and take shelter in him.
Now I feel like a bird that fell out of its nest.
No, my daughter...
I know... I know, my daughter.
But...
...that bird did not fall off its nest.
She left its nest to build its own nest.
And now...
...she will build her own nest,
she will be stronger than before.
You won't be alone when
you are starting your family.
I will always be with you, my daughter.
You were always with me.
My mother was not with me...
...but you were.
Now if you allow me...
...I want to call you "mother".
Does anyone ever ask for permission
to call their mother "mother"?
Yes.
Yes..
My beautiful daughter...
I'm grateful... I'm grateful
you're Aladdin's mother.
Thankfully, you are our mother.
Bala mother..
Say that again.
Bala mother...
You understood me, right?
Tonight, you will put this in
Gonca and Alaeddin's room.
Every breath they take will bring
them closer to death step by step.
Why is that Hatun here again?
It's obvious that she's not
here for something good.
Cerkutay, I want all the information about Mekece.
Where are the enters and exits
and how many soldiers are there?
Where they put the archers.
Inform me about all of this.
Yes, my Bey. We'll start
the duty when the night falls.
But, my Bey.
Sorry for my curiosity.
We sent all the alps to the
tribe, it seems we won't besiege.
My Bey.
What's on your mind?
We'll see who is the soldier and who is not.
We will hunt them down.
Now they smile at us.
But I know that this is not the truth.
Even if they find out that Alaeddin is
innocent, Ibrahim Bey and Yakup Bey
will definitely cause a problem.
Anger has blinded them, my Bey.
One for his dead son and one
for his daughter who ran away.
The truth will slap them in the face.
Mekece will be our land with Allah's permission.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
-Konur Bey.
-My Shahzade.
-My Shahzade?
-Boran Bey.
My Shahzade.
Praise be! Praise be!
Osman Bey, Cerkutay, are they alright?
-Thankfully, they are alright.
-They are alright.
Ibrahim and Yakup Bey did not
trust us enough to come close to them.
When I found out about their
Mekece move, it was too late.
But they will pay for this treachery.
Let us get rid of the doubts.
Their doubts will be gone
and they will trust you more.
When you capture Ulcay, they will fall
for the trap and trust you so much that
from now on they will want
to do everything with you.
I hope so.
Children, listen to me very carefully.
We will not kneel to them nor
we will leave the castle to them.
-Alaeddin.
-My Bey.
Take Gonca and Holofira and take goods to Bursa.
Your route will be the borders of Mekece.
Yes, my Bey.
Yakup and Ibrahim Bey
won't like it and try to stop it.
They will send support units from
the castle and stop the caravan.
That's my sons.
That's exactly what's going to happen.
So that the castle will be empty
and the conquest will be easier.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
You will tie the rope
around that jackal named
Ulcay's neck and you'll
take him to the tribe.
Boran
And Konur.
Gather information from them and attack his den.
It is time to find out
who's he collaborating with.
Yes, my Bey.
My Bey.
What about Gunduz Bey?
He's obviously offended.
It's not right for a Bey to act
so reckless in the battlefield.
Especially if he's my child's father-in-law.
-Let him rest in the tribe for a while.
-Okay, my Bey.
Come on.
Their dens...
...will become their grave.
-I hope so, my Shahzade.
-Come on.
Won't you say welcome?
Bala Hatun?
You haven't been very pleasant since the
day you came to the frontiers, Melike Hatun.
This time I'm here for something well.
Haven't you heard yet? Mekece has become our land.
We're neighbours.
Right, we've heard it.
We've also heard how you took it.
I hope you're not offended.
Anyway.
Since Ibrahim Bey and Yakup Bey talked to Osman
Bey and agreed on it, the hostility is over.
The hostility is over.
You also found the killer of your child Ahmed.
Then what do you want from us, Melike Hatun?
Are we going to talk about it here?
Should I teach you how to host a guest?
Come on, get inside.
Go to hell.
There's a raid!
-Allah is the Greatest!
Allah is the Greatest!
Konur, what are you doing with these guys?
You betrayed Ibrahim Bey.
I've never been in the same path with Ibrahim Bey.
How can one be with these jackals?
It's not clear who's holding their leashes.
They are jackals, but...
...they are loyal.
They are honorable.
They don't laugh in your face
and do things behind your back.
They are letting whoever wants to
shed blood in this land pull the strings.
Husrev. Walking in the same path with these
dastards is deviating from the path of Haqq
-Konur!
-Husrev.
Konur Bey is right.
They killed Shahzade Ahmed
dishonorably to cause a war.
Now.
Now, you'll make a decision here.
Either you'll die
and rot here with them.
Or you will fight by our side in the path
of Haqq against the dishonorable ones.
Osman Bey.
Let me accompany you to dinner.
You did a big job..
..by finding Ahmed's killer.
I only did my duty.
Your son..
..has been found innocent as well.
My son was not guilty to begin with.
We need to know whoever..
..is trying to put us against each other.
Ask those questions to Ibrahim Bey and Yakup Bey.
I only follow orders.
That is the real issue.
Whose orders are you following?
We will see that.
I both saved your life and your son's
You are still acting like an enemy to me.
You need to be my equal first..
..to be my enemy.
Are you my equal to be my enemy?
Now, whoever attacked Ahmed..
..attacked the judge as well.
I am not like others you know.
I know the truth well.
When truth is revealed..
..then I will declare my sentence.
Let us kill Osman while he is here.
Who can stand against us?
Orhan or Alaeddin?
Who can stand against Candarlis and Germiyanids?
You are right, my Mehmed.
No one can stand.
However, we need to think this through.
We will make such plans..
..that leaderless Kayi will follow us.
Commander of Bursa and
castle lords are on their way.
They are coming here.
We will gather all forces in our hands.
Tomorrow, you will go to greet them.
Both power, and trade.
Osman will get stuck in a corner.
He will get stuck so much that..
.he will not have any other
option to bow down to us.
I will bring them here.
Yakup Bey, let us go to Gunduz Bey's tribe as well.
I already sent words to alps.
Let us get into Gunduz Bey's head so much..
..that he will fall to wherever we want.
Your mind is something else, Ibrahim Bey.
Thank you.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you too.
Here, please.
Beys, what is this?
Did you stray away from your traditions?
Did you forget to sit on the floor?
What is this table?
We do not learn traditions from you.
We are not bound to this table as well.
We have work to do.
Sit down.
New things, Osman Bey.
You will get used to it as well. Come on, sit.
Authority does not corrupt anyone.
It only reveals what a person
is really inside, Ibrahim Bey.
It seems, this is who you really are.
By working with this infidel..
..you got used to their traditions.
-Brother?
-Tell me, Alaeddin.
So you are still mad at me.
You think so.
Sorry.
I., you know.. I can't keep my mouth shut.
You are not the only one,
Alaeddin. Fatma is like you as well.
-It seems I am being tested with you.
-Don't say that.
Am I that bad, brother?
No one can hold you back.
You have to say the truth boldly.
I said the wrong thing, with the burden of duty.
I didn't think Gunduz Bey would be offended.
I know, Alaeddin.
What Gunduz Bey did was wrong.
However, manners.
Manners is of great importance to us, Alaeddin.
Do not think that I am protecting Gunduz Bey.
I would've said the same
thing if it was another Bey.
Especially in a war time like this.
We need to not offend the Beys that are with us.
You are right, brother.
After my duty is done, I will
make peace with Gunduz Bey.
You forgive me as well, alright?
-My brother.
-Thanks to Allah, brother. Thanks to Allah.
Well, Boran Bey.
Like old times, huh? Come on.
Start playing kopuz.
Alright, my Shahzade.
Here we go. Well...
Well...
Praise be!
Well sung, Boran Bey!
You excited us about fighting!
Thank you, my Shahzade.
Let's talk about the matter.
It's not a good time to be stubborn.
Our land has gone through hard times.
Now we have a great chance.
The trade route to be opened from
east to west will be under our control.
People will be at ease as
long as peace is provided.
Great Beys are speaking so well.
But they don't speak of the rest.
You tell us then.
So we can know, Osman Bey.
Our trade from east to west...
Tell me what the east is.
Olcaytu.
The Ilkhanid State. They
caused Great Seljuks to collapse.
They destroyed our tribes and killed our children.
Well...
So you want to grow bigger...
...by trading with them, huh?
And what about the west?
Byzantine attempted to...
...send an army of Crusaders to
our lands just a few months ago.
They killed our children.
We should have no peace and no deals with them.
It seems you want to let
the heathens have the bridle.
Nobody can bridle us, Osman Bey.
Don't be worrying.
What you're saying is all the past, Osman Bey.
What is past is past.
Don't be one of those who look
behind but can't see forward, Osman Bey.
Either be with us or be nothing.
We won't let you trade.
Do whatever you can!
The move you're trying to make...
...will let the dying Byzantine rise again.
It'll give a chance to Olcaytu who is
looking for a chance to jump on us!
No.
I will never give you
permission to do this to my land.
Nobody needs your permission, Osman.
We did what we did.
It's your turn to decide.
If you pledge loyalty and obey us,
...you will prosper with us.
If you don't
...you will vanish.
We have two ways ahead of us.
But either of the ways..
...will destroy us.
The right to do is...
...standing against you.
I will let nobody have an easy victory.
Then, Osman Bey...
Your fate is determined.
It's me who will determine your fates.
Like you determined Boran's and Konur's fates?
Those men fought behind you for years.
You can't even make your own men listen to you.
But you are showing off to Beys here.
Look at that jackal.
He thinks he can speak freely here.
I will treat my land..
...just as I treat my soldiers.
If someone makes a mistake,
...I will mind no other
things and just cut him off!
They made a mistake and now are paying for it.
Just wait.
You will pay for what you did as well.
You will make me pay, Osman Bey?
Your justice can't harm my skin.
I'm not one of your people.
Justice is only for us.
And for you
...there is only a sharp sword.
You'll see.
You will see.
You're waiting for your time.
Osman Bey, pull yourself together.
You're threatening my soldiers in front of me!
He's not threatening only
me but also you, Ibrahim Bey!
Ulcay!
Get out.
What is your final decision, Osman Bey?
If you accept, we will become
much stronger together, Osman Bey.
The fight never stops but just waits for its time.
Stand behind my father.
And be stronger.
Thank you, boys.
Thank you.
Obviously, you fathers
will never walk in this way...
...even if they see the truth.
But you will see.
Soon, you'll see the poison under the cruel.
The battle does not wait for anything.
Have a blessed night.
It will be your last peaceful night.
This night, the battle will
definitely begin with Osman's death.
His children will attack
Germiyan and Candaroglus for revenge.
You made him attack Osman.
You gained their trust and caused
suspicion in bashibozouk soldiers.
This night
you will take Osman to me silently.
I'll send Osman's head
to Olcaytu.
So, long story short,
I forgive you, Gonca.
Is that so?
We didn't do anything that you should forgive.
I forgive you too, Holofira.
We don't have any reason to seek forgiveness.
You do, but
but since you're naive, I won't dwell on it.
Anyway
We will unite against all of
the enemies in these lands.
Right. That's right, but
I'm a bit confused.
Who's the enemy, Melike Hatun?
You united with the Lords.
While you have Holofira on your
table are you asking for an enemy?
Isn't Holofira Byzantine?
Right, Holofira?
So not all the Byzantines are enemies.
Those we can get along with
are friends, the others are enemies.
Holofira is a daughter of
this household, Melike Hatun.
She's our daughter.
Since we're friends from now on...
...then we need to find the
traitor who tried to kill my child...
and who killed Rukneddin The Judge
and replaced him with a fake judge.
Of course.
We're also very curious
about who did this treachery.
Who's that?
Who wanted to kill Alaeddin?
It must be someone who doesn't trust justice.
Someone who knew judge
would find Alaeddin innocent.
Right. You're right.
Maybe that Byzantine infidel who killed my son
and shed his blood did this treachery
We cannot know where the
treachery come from, Melike Hatun.
How could a Byzantinian know your judge...
...that replace him with the fake one.
Isn't that right?
Right.
That's true.
If Allah permits,
we will sing our folk songs in Bursa.
If Allah permits, if Allah permits.
When Allah give us the chance, your crown
will drop even if you're the king in Bursa.
We will succeed, if Allah permits.
-We will turn my father's dreams into reality.
-If Allah permits, my brother.
Orhan Bey.
Alaeddin Bey.
I knew that you and Osman
Bey were on the right path.
But I'm sure now.
Tell me
I'm ready to do anything for you.
Thank you, Husrev. Thank you.
Then...
...you'll do a very important duty for us.
Just name it. What's that duty?
You'll be...
...our key to Mekece.
What smells in here?
What kind of smell is this?
Let's see what will you do when
you don't have a sword to use.
What are you doing here at this hour, kiddo?
Who am I talking to?
What are you doing here...
Stop, wait!
What are you doing?
Don't you know what will happen to you if
you cut my Osman Bey's right-hand man.
Cerkutay Bey. Cerkutay.
Where am I? What's this place?
Cerkutay Bey, you were sleepwalking again.
This jackal would have killed
you if I hadn't gotten there.
Was he going to kill me?
It suits him to kill a man without a sword.
He's a jackal after all.
Don't get in my way.
Or I'll crush you
both like a rat.
Get out of here.
I wish you hadn't woken me, Aykurt.
I would have killed him in my sleep.
Look at me.
I don't have customs.
I don't have a rule.
I don't care that you're a
guest and I'll kill you both here.
Get out of here.
Our swords will meet soon.
Be patient.
Aykurt, let's go.
I haven't seen her since I came,
where's your other daughter-in-law Bala?
Elcim daughter is in Yenisehir, she has a duty.
She wouldn't want to be here, of course.
Come on then.
Be our guest tonight, Melike Hatun.
Hatuns prepared your tent.
Thank you, my beautiful daughter.
Beys are doing politics.
They cannot think with compassion
and mercy. It's their nature.
But from now on, we, Turkmen women...
...won't allow brotherly blood to be shed, huh?
I hope so, Melike Hatun.
That's been the intention of
us, the Kayi tribe since the past.
I am sorry, my Gonca daughter.
Holofira. I was in pain, I
expect you to forgive me.
When someone loses her
child, she also loses her mind.
Good night. -Good night.
Mother..
Do you really believe this woman?
Only Allah knows if her intention is good.
We will still be careful, my daughter.
You will also be on alert.
Ertolga!
Go to Yakup Bey and Ibrahim Bey.
Our door will always be open.
They can come. -Yes, Gunduz Bey.
The conqueror of many castles...
...the killer of many brave Byzantium soldiers...
...Osman Bey...
...is now a harmless puppy.
Are you ready, my soldiers?
Today, we will witness the
destruction of a Turkish legend!
The strongest man among the Turks...
...history will write that he
died with my sword today.
Even if your head is needed
by others, I will take your life.
You will die by my sword, Osman!
You dog!
Are you going to kill me, huh? You won't
even be able to see Mekece's conquest!
Not protection, conquest!
Cerkutay! If you hadn't noticed the poison,
we would have been in a difficult position.
Since I track the scent of food, my
nose has a good sense of smell my Bey.
I have also caught the scent
of these dogs' trap, for sure.
Ahmed...
My son...
My son.
Wake up, my son...
Stand up..
Come on, wake up.
Mother...
Kill my killer, mother.
Where is Ahmed?
What did you do to my son?
Kill my killer.
Where is my son? Where is Ahmed? Where is my son?
Kill my killer, mother.
It's because of you... You were the reason!
It's because of you!
Ahmed! Ahmed!
What do Kayis want, Andra?
Holofira and Gonca Hatun..
They will take the goods to
Bursa and Iznik to do business.
They are getting ready.
Ibrahim Bey showed his
foresight by sending us here.
And we will do as he ordered and watch their steps.
Now... we have to prevent this business.
Go and inform Ibrahim Bey now.
Stop!
Don't tell him that Gonca will go there as well.
Yakup Bey should not stop
him because of his daughter.
My son is under the soil because of them.
And I will do my best until
I bring the end of Kayis.
I swear..
Did you get all the information
regarding the conquest of the castle?
I have all of them my Bey. Here.
Thank you.
Mekece, huh?
Mekece...
Damn it.
You could not die, Osman. You are still alive!
Here... Before tomorrow night...
..this place will be ours if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Mekece...
Lord Matheus!
He is hanged in the courtyard of his own property.
What did you do, Osman?
Who was he allied with?
Why did you kill the Lord?!
He had poison put into the lantern in my room.
He asked me to come.
He tried to kill me!
And I killed him.
Now tell me.
Which one of you were
holding the leash of this dog?
We didn't know about this!
Apparently, he
did this on his own.
If you worked with him...
...then I will see you as infidels, know that!
But if you tell me that you fell into
heedlessness and that's why you let him...
...then the one who falls into
heedlessness can never stand by our side!
That dog's blood watered this soil.
Now this place is about to be our homeland.
You know...
In times of war, peace is never made!
Your own fist is better than a stranger's food.
I will make you learn this by force if necessary.
This is not a place of friends anymore.
This is not the land of Turks anymore!
With Allah's permission, I will..
..make this place Turks' land.
-Pull yourself together Osman!
-You pull yourself together!
I will make you learn. Come
on, this is not the time to talk.
Are you declaring war on us, Osman?
Come on, Osman. Start that war already.
"So do not take them as allies.."
"..unless they emigrate in the cause of Allah."
...Then seize them.."
"..and kill them wherever you find them.
"Do not befriend them.."
"..nor get help from them."
[4:89]
We act on the command of Qur-an.
This place will be conquered for real again!
Let this be known.
Now, Osman will cause chaos.
Osman...
..is sending goods to Bursa with a caravan.
So he will both declare war on us..
..and make business with Bursa at the same time.
No. I will never allow this.
Ulcay!
First..
..send men after the caravan
that is heading to Bursa.
Then, take Konur and Boran with you.
They know Yenisehir the best.
You know what to do.
I will make Yenisehir worse
than Karacahisar Marketplace.
Caravan's road is close to us.
There will a good ambush.
Come on.
Yakup Bey.
I say, we diminish Osman..
..before he prepares the field of battle.
You are right.
Let us go and make peace with Gunduz Bey.
Let them diminish..
..and let us grow.
Let us see what will Gunduz Bey say.
Take that lord down.
-We couldn't talk, Gonca.
-Everything happened so fast..
..I feel like it was a dream, Holofira.
I hope the nightmare part of your life is over.
It will be like a good dream to you now.
I hope so. However, I pray for both of us.
I want you to be good as well.
They are coming.
Halt.
It is forbidden for Kayi caravan to enter Bursa.
With which permission? I am
Princess Holofira, open the road.
Princess, what kind of Roman are
you, travelling with these barbarians?
-Have you no shame?
-Watch your words, commander!
-I have nothing to be ashamed of. -Princess.
-This is my last warning.
-Or what?
Or I will kill all of you without hesitation.
Turks do not fear! We do not give up!
We will see who dies and who lives!
Come on, alps!
-Allah is the greatest!
-Attack!
Come here!
-I've come my Gonca.
-Don't worry.
-I've waited for you to come.
-Really now?
Come on then.
It is time to hunt.
We will make a move and stop Osman's trade.
-Finally.
-And how will we do that?
We will attack Yenisehir.
Come on, let us gather some men.
Come on!
The day Ahmed died, you were after us.
You will talk now.
Get up.
Alaeddin!
Alps, get back!
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
My Gonca, we will go to the
castle. You go back to the tribe.
My Gonca.
The day we feared so much has come, Alaeddin.
The war has started. Now, my father on one side..
..and we are on the other.
I know your worry.
I am on the road to clash with your brother.
However, I know.
Yakup Bey will see the truth.
What if he does not? Then
what will we do, Alaeddin?
Come on alps!
Gonca, are you alright?
This is such a war, Holofira.
My father and brother on one side..
..and the man I love, my heart on the other.
No matter who wins this war..
..I will get hurt.
Come on.
-Peace be upon you
-Peace be upon you, Gunduz Bey.
Peace be upon you too. Welcome.
Gunduz Bey, you must be wondering...
...why we are here.
We wanted Osman Bey to be our guest.
But he declared war against us.
Is that appropriate, Gunduz Bey?
And you want me...
..to choose a side in this war, huh?
Whoever takes no sides...
...will be removed aside, Gunduz Bey.
If you don't want to lose
...you have to choose.
The wolf has raided...
...the nest of the jackal, Ulcay.
-Orhan...
Yes, Orhan.
You will pay a heavy price, though.
We will see.
-You don't care about your life.
-Whose dog are you?
I swear I will make wolves eat you.
You jackal!
-It's like you're attacking heathens, Konur Bey.
-You say so?
Old man, I need you alive.
I have things to do with you.
I swear I will catch you.
Ulcay, you can't run off!
Just run, Ulcay. Let's see how far you can go.
Osman.
Ibrahim Bey will make you pay
a heavy price for this, Osman.
Shut up!
You think you're still Ibrahim Bey's man?
I killed Lord. You took
Ibrahim Bey's soldiers captive.
If you don't let me go,
there will be a war to come.
We've never been afraid of war! Ever!
But just be patient. When Ibrahim Bey finds out...
...who is holding your leash
...he will want to kill you personally.
There is nothing you can take from me, Osman.
I will never serve you.
Kill me here when you have a chance.
Or you will regret.
You helped us and you will again.
We'll enter Mekece thanks to you.
-Oghuz!
-My Bey.
Take this...
...and the ones behind him to the tribe.
Beat them well.
-Make them ready to speak to me.
-As you order, my Bey.
My Bey, give Ulcay to me. He
and I have an unfinished business.
Solgur Agha.
-Just be patient.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Come on.
-Take him, Oghuz.
Well, son..
It's time to make Mekece the land of Turks.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-Let's go.
Let's get on horses.
I have a question for you, Gunduz Bey.
Osman gave you everything you wanted.
But still, you wanted your daughter...
...to marry his son. Why?
For the same reason...
...why you wanted your daughter to marry...
...Ibrahim Bey's son. Now you answer.
Because I know the strength comes from unity.
Well... That's it.
If you choose our side
...we'll offer you greater strength, Gunduz Bey.
-I hear you. -Orhan...
...is your son-in-law.
If you take our side, our job will be easier.
Osman will have no power left to resist.
But if he still resists
...then Kayi will obey your orders.
What makes you really
think I'm going to accept this?
Don't you see...
...Osman is putting people in danger, Gunduz Bey?
He's declaring war against us.
Don't you see the consequences?
You have no chances to win...
...while Lords support us.
Gunduz Bey.
You should stand on our side.
So Kayi people will have a shadow
to stay under when the war begins.
We have no problems with Kayi.
We have a problem with Osman. Join us.
We can stop him together.
Protect your people from this war.
Reduce the brother's blood.
If it's inevitable, it's good to reduce.
What about the trade?
That's it, Gunduz Bey. Let's
speak the same language.
If you take our side
..we'll let you be a sharer.
A lion's share for the lion, Gunduz Bey.
-Don't be worrying.
-Thank you, thank you.
We're together then.
Let's leave to welcome our guests then.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Who are the guests?
How did it happen, Husrev? Where did you catch him?
He had a grudge with Ulcay,
...attempted to raid the settlement...
...and fell into the jackal's trap.
What a strange world! Since when has the
wolf been falling into the jackal's trap?
Put Osman Bey in the dungeon. Beys
will deliver a judgement when they come.
As long as you seek vengeance
...you will always lose.
And you? Who is behind you?
Look into my eyes! Look!
Do I look like a man who
would leave a Turk's fate to you?
They're looking for a chance
to break you, Osman Bey.
Well... Not like you.
They're still our enemy.
We're not here to be captive...
...but to capture Mekece.
Orhan.
Alaaddin.
Don't. Don't you take
another step towards my father.
Archers, attack! Kill them all!
How could this happen?
It's time for a guard change.
Before Osman Bey arrives, we'll
climb up and put on their clothes.
My Bey!
What is it, Commander? You
already started stepping back.
Soldiers, attack!
We have never been
captives since the day we were
born. We will not be slaves
to anyone from now on!
Alps! Go everywhere! Don't let any of them survive!
Close the doors! protect
the castle! No one will get in!
While investigating, we encountered the monks.
We heard that the
person Melike Hatun killed
because she claimed he
was the killer of her son...
...was actually a convict
sentenced to death in Bursa.
He escaped just three days after the murder.
How is that possible?
-Why, my daughter?
He was going to die anyway.
They turned his death...
...into a cheap show for someone's benefit.
So, Ahmet Bey's killer is still out there.
Thanks to this information...
...you're preventing a major
war, Yunus Emre. Thank you.
There's more, Bala Hatun. The fake judge...
...was the judge in Kastamonu
during the Cobanogullari era.
He was dismissed from his position for...
...going against justice and engaging in haram.
Kastamonu?
Then Candaroglu must be involved.
Why would Candaroglu prevent them
from finding his own children's killer?
Because he has already made...
...his judgment in his own court.
He doesn't want his verdict to be proven wrong.
He wants justice to prevail...
...but it's his justice that he seeks.
His arrogance is so great
that it magnifies his pain.
And that pain makes him
think that he has the right to...
...do everything.
Especially when it's a...
...grieving mother accusing
someone as her son's murder...
Ah, Melike Hatun, ah...
May it be good.
Alps are coming!
Boran Bey and Konur Bey are captives!
Bala Hatun! The captives are coming!
Boran Bey and Konur Bey are coming!
Take your last breaths, Gonca.
I will send you to hell.
Olcay... He got caught.
He will never speak.
These three of them are
now our captives, Bala Hatun.
Stop!
While these men were in our service..
-...how can you...
Don't you say something, Melike Hatun.
Stay out of this.
Oghuz Alp. Take these dogs to the square.
Tie them up.
Start questioning them.
-Yes, Bala Hatun.
Walk! -Traitors!
That Olcay dog was involved in your son's death.
We just want justice, Melike Hatun.
So that you came here for peace...
...you should know that
we are doing this for peace.
Or else... you can leave.
Come on, Alps! We are going there!
Hang on, brothers! Hang on!
Step back, Osman Bey. Don't make
me do things that I don't want to do.
You are quite impulsive.
You will die and it will be a pity.
-Listen to him, Tugay.
Drop your sword.
-My duty is to protect the castle!
It is the order of my Bey. If I
need to die, I will die for sure.
But I will not give the castle to you, Osman Bey.
Even though you stayed
with your father Ibrahim Bey...
...you still have a bit of..
...morals and conscience in you.
I do as my Bey says. But if a Turk Bey...
...ever faces the sword of infidels
I never step back, Osman Bey.
Don't fight for no reason. The castle has fallen.
Surrender, so you can survive, Alps.
Drop your swords.
Calm down, brother.
May your new castle be blessed,
Osman Bey! The castle has fallen!
Victory is ours with Allah's permission!
Allah is the Greatest!
-Allah is the Greatest!
Thank you, thank you.
Long live.
But the property only belongs to Allah.
We are just protecting the trust.
Come here.
Take him to the dungeon.
Let him think about who should he support.
-Where are you going?
-I'll put our banner where it belongs.
Alright, alright.
But stop, wait. Let the Beys come.
-If Allah permits, we will put it after that.
-Yes, my Bey.
I bring you greetings from holy Rome.
Thank you, Commander.
We brought you the glorious Bey of Kayi
Gunduz Bey.
He is Orhan's father-in-law.
He's a glorious fighter.
Great. Then we have many
things to talk about, Beys.
-Let's go to the castle.
-Come on.
We need to get out of here
before Osman Bey arrives.
This tribe was once your tribe, Boran.
Why are you in a hurry?
Look how frightened they look.
When we get out of here,
they will drown in their blood.
I know Osman very well. He didn't just capture us.
He captured Ibrahim
Bey and Yakup Bey as well.
If you know him well,
tell me. What does he want?
He's trying to pin Shahzade Ahmed's death on us.
That Byzantine killed Ahmed
everyone can witness to it.
But we don't know who's he serving to, Konur.
Osman will find a fake evidence
and make everyone believe.
You're right.
It's clear where they will find those evidence.
-Rukneddin The Judge death is a mystery.
-That's right.
Is it possible for Byzantines
to kill a judge in these lands?
Enough!
You've bothered me.
It is possible to kill without making it obvious.
I can see it now.
How did Orhan find Rukneddin The Judge?
What if the murderer serves Osman?
He knew about what we did.
Brother, this dastard knew about everything.
Kill them, traitors!
When the blood feud of Shahzade Ahmed is over
Kayis women sheathed their swords.
Women.
When the swords are unsheathed
they won't be sheathed until
they cut your head, dastard.
But first, you'll talk.
Everyone will find out the evil things he did.
Mouthy woman.
I didn't do anything without
Ibrahim Bey's knowledge.
Isn't that right, Melike Hatun?
They'd say one would change. I know you,
but if you played any
tricks, they will be revealed.
-Ulcay.
-Don't trust these witches.
They're not the murderers of their child
-but they're as guilty as the murderer.
-Enough!
You can't spit your poison anymore.
Oguz Alp.
Even if you strip my flesh from my bones
you won't be able to wash this blood off you.
Don't waste your breath in vain.
You'll talk when Osman Bey comes anyway.
Either gladly or with torture.
But the truth will be revealed.
Osman.
Gunduz Bey. Did you welcome the Beys well?
As you requested,
we welcomed them very well, Osman Bey.
We didn't offend anyone...
...and we had a great conversation.
Alright, alright. You did well.
Now I'll welcome them in my property Mekece.
We'll sit altogether and we'll
talk about the evil alliance.
We will all see whose head will...
...remain on his body...
...and whose will fall.
Visit turkision.com for more!